Melville S. Munro Papers MS036
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic history of Tufts College, 1904 -- 1946; MS036.001; 20.8 Linear Feet; 329 Digital Object(s)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 52, 1937-05 -- 1937-06; MS036.001.070.00001 (Volume 70)
    - Martha Dowse, Captain of Tufts Archery Team, 1937; MS036.001.070.00001.03342; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 70)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 52, Box No. 70, Pg. 30
      People; Athletics; Archery; photographic print; Dowse, Martha; Jackson College
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 53, 1937-09 -- 1937-10; MS036.001.071.00001 (Volume 71)
    - Cyril J. Jones, Raymond Bancroft, A. Robert Killam, Ward Albro, and John Sullivan, class of 1941 Liberal Arts students, 1937 -- 1938; MS036.001.071.00001.04403; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 71)
      Dates are approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 071, p. 24, #13107
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Jones, Cyril Johnstone; Bancroft, Raymond; Killam, A. Robert; Albro, Ward; Sullivan, John
    - Frank R. Pote, Harry Ober, John M. McNaught, Arthur Milhench, and Francis P. Hazel, Class of 1941 Liberal Arts students, 1937 -- 1938; MS036.001.071.00001.04404; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 71)
      Dates are approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 071, p. 27, #13119
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Pote, Frank R.; Ober, Harry; McNaught, John; Milhench, Arthur L.
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., Donald T. Shedd, Lawrence B. Bennett, Nicholas Martin, and John Donlan, class of 1941 engineering students, 1937 -- 1938; MS036.001.071.00001.04405; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 71)
      Dates are approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 071, p. 37, #13155
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.; Shedd, Donald T.; Bennett, Lawrence B.; Martin, Nicholas; Donlan, John
    - William Lynch, William Jones, Jr., Paul Bixby, William A. Ritter, and Gordon Winchester, class of 1941 engineering students, 1937 -- 1938; MS036.001.071.00001.04406; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 71)
      Date is approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 071, p. 38, #13159
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Lynch, William; Jones, William Johnstone, Jr.; Bixby, Paul; Ritter, William A.; Winchester, Gordon
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 54, 1937-10 -- 1937-12; MS036.001.072.00001 (Volume 72)
    - Professor W.C. Casson climbing into his Austin car, 1932-01-12; MS036.001.072.00001.01701; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 51)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 55, 1937-11 -- 1938-01; MS036.001.073.00001 (Volume 73)
    - Professor James A. Reynolds of the Electrical Engineering Department giving a lesson, 1938; MS036.001.073.00001.02817; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 73)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 55, Box No. 73, Pg. 135
      People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; Reynolds, James A.; Dept. of Electrical Engineering
    - Tufts Track Twins Cyril Jones and William Jones, Jr., 1937; MS036.001.073.00001.03473; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 73)
      (left to right) Cyril Jones and William Jones, Jr.); Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 55, Box No. 73, Pg. 139.
      Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Jones, Cyril Johnstone; Jones, William Johnstone, Jr.; Track
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 58, 1938-04 -- 1938-06; MS036.001.074.00001 (Volume 74)
    - Joe Lippincott listening to radio, 1938; MS036.001.074.00001.02847; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 74)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, Box 074, April 1938 - June 1938, #13779
      People; Students; photographic print; Lippincott, Joseph
    - The "Varsity" String Quartet, 1938; MS036.001.074.00001.02848; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 74)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, Box 074, April 1938 - June 1938, #13842
      People; Students; Student activities; photographic print
    - Dr. Carleton Ames Wheeler tunes in for the foreign short wave programs on the radio, 1930; MS036.001.074.00001.03475; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 74)
      Munro box 74, p. 85
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Wheeler, Carleton Ames; Dept. of Romance Languages
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., 1938; MS036.001.074.00001.04407; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 74)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 074, p. 46, #13815
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.
    - Goddard Hall, Fletcher School Auditorium, 1938; MS036.001.074.00001.04658; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 124)
      image is from Munro collection, box 074, page 10, #10539.
      Rooms; Interior views; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
    - Wilson House play room, 1938; MS036.001.074.00001.04659; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 124)
      image is from Munro collection, box 074, page 9, #13325.
    - Goddard Gymnasium, 1938; MS036.001.074.00001.04660; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 20)
      image is from Munro collection, box 074, page 10, #99-d.
      Athletics; Gymnasiums; Interior views; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 56, 1938-01 -- 1938-03; MS036.001.075.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 75)
    Alpha Tau Omega, 45.
    - Dean Edith L. Bush, 1938-03-03; MS036.001.075.00001.02670; Unknown (Volume 75)
      contained in MS036/001, box:075 - Melville S. Munro, Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 56 (January - March 1938), pg. 116
      People; Deans; photographic print; Bush, Edith L.; Jackson College
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 57, 1937-01 -- 1938-04; MS036.001.076.00001 (Volume 76)
    - Tufts student Marynoyes Kellogg, 1937; MS036.001.076.00001.02845; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 76)
      Photographic History of Tufts College, Box 076, January 1937- April 1938, #13689
      People; Students; photographic print; Kellogg, Marynoyes
    - Jackson's "World Fair" winners, Eleanor Magee, Marynoyes Kellogg, Rhoda MacKenzie, and Jane Parker, 1937; MS036.001.076.00001.02846; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 76)
      Photographic history of Tufts College, Box 076, January 1937 - April 1938, #13683
      People; Students; photographic print; Kellogg, Marynoyes; Magee, Eleanor; MacKenzie, Rhoda; Parker, Jane
    - Tufts indoor track racers, 1937 -- 1938; MS036.001.076.00001.04408; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 76)
      Dates are approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 076, p. 16, #13532
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., "A Master of Track Technique", 1937 -- 1938; MS036.001.076.00001.04409; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 76)
      Dates are approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 076, p. 18, #13537
      Students; Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 62, 1939-03 -- 1939-04; MS036.001.077.00001 (Volume 77)
    - Eddie Dugger, 1939; MS036.001.077.00001.04412; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 77)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 077, p. 20 #13914
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 59, 1938-04 -- 1938-10; MS036.001.078.00001 (Volume 78)
    Alumni day photos and news clippings, pp42-43
    - Fallen elm tree on East Hall, 1938; MS036.001.078.00001.03451; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 78)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 59, Box No. 78, Pg. 99
      Buildings; Dormitories; photographic print
    - Fallen elm tree on East Hall, 1938; MS036.001.078.00001.03452; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 78)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 59, Box 78, Pg. 99
    - Theodore Nouman, Vincent P. Perlo, Herbert A. Mann, Harold Rubin, and Vinson B. Conliffe, 1938 -- 1939; MS036.001.078.00001.04411; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 78)
      Date is approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 078, p. 130 #19377
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Mouman, Theodore; Perlo, Vincent P.; Mann, Herbert A.; Rubin, Harold; Conliffe, Vinson B.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 60, 1938-10 -- 1938-12; MS036.001.079.00001 (Volume 79)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 61, 1938-11 -- 1939-02; MS036.001.080.00001 (Volume 80)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 63, 1939-04 -- 1939-06; MS036.001.081.00001 (Volume 81)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 65, 1939-10 -- 1939-12; MS036.001.082.00001 (Volume 82)
    - Dr. Eric Walker puzzles over a high tension lab set-up, October, 1939; MS036.001.082.00001.01704; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 65)
      (contained in Photographic History of Tufts College, Vol. 65, pg. 7, box 82)
      People; photographic print; Walker, Eric
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 64, 1939-05 -- 1939-10; MS036.001.083.00001 (Volume 83)
    Alumni day photos, news release, and news clippings, pp 32-38
    - Outdoor track squad, 1939; MS036.001.083.00001.04413; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 83)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 083, p. 1 #14557
    - A group of Tufts record breakers, 1939; MS036.001.083.00001.04414; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 83)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 83, p. 2, #14558.
      Athletics; Students; Track; photographic print; Black students
    - Edward Dugger, Jr. and William Atkinson, 1939; MS036.001.083.00001.04415; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 83)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 83, p. 3, #14556
      Students; Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.; Atkinson, William
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., 1939; MS036.001.083.00001.04416; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 83)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 83, p. 8, #14559
      Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., 1939; MS036.001.083.00001.04417; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 83)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 83, p. 8, #14560
      photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.
    - Alexander Logan, Robert R. Powers, Tom Sharry, David Hazel, and H. R. Fiege, 1939; MS036.001.083.00001.04418; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 83)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 83, p. 88A, #14668
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Logan, Alexander; Powers, Robert R.; Sharry, Tom; Hazel, David; Fiege, H. R.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 66, 1939-12 -- 1940-03; MS036.001.084.00001 (Volume 84)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 67, 1940-02 -- 1940-03; MS036.001.085.00001 (Volume 85)
    - Unbeaten Tufts indoor track squad, 1940; MS036.001.085.00001.04431; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 85)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 085, p. 30, #14989
      Track (Men's); photographic print; Black students
    - Coach Clarence Dussault, Edward Dugger, Jr., Walter Hall, and William Atkinson, 1940; MS036.001.085.00001.04432; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 85)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 085, p. 72, #14981
      photographic print; Dussault, Clarence "Ding"; Dugger, Edward, Jr.; Hall, Walter; Atkinson, William
    - New students: Kenneth D. Holmer, Eugene M. Lyons, Stanley S. Schultz, Henry W. Nartel, Earle W. Tuttle, and Eric K. Bergstrom, 1946; MS036.001.085.00001.04434; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 85)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 085, p. 81
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Holmer, Kenneth D.; Lyons, Eugene M.; Schultz, Stanley S.; Nartel, Henry W.; Tuttle, Earle W.; Bergstrom, Eric K.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 68, 1940-04 -- 1940-06; MS036.001.086.00001 (Volume 86)
    Alpha Tau Omega, p48.
    - Fletcher School student body, 1940; MS036.001.086.00001.04655; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 124)
      image is from Munro collection, box 086, page 35, #15140.
      Students; Graduate students; People; photographic print; Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy; Tufts University
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 69, 1940-06; MS036.001.087.00001 (Volume 87)
    Alumni day photos, news releases and clippings, pp 109-118
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., May, 1940; MS036.001.087.00001.04427; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 87)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 087, p. 53, #15178
      Track (Men's); Athletics; photographic print; Black students; Dugger, Edward, Jr.
    - Faculty and students of the Crane School of Religion in front of Goddard Chapel, June, 1940; MS036.001.087.00001.04428; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 87)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 087, p. 54, #15168
      photographic print; Black students
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., June, 1940; MS036.001.087.00001.04429; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 87)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 087, p. 58, #15780
    - Edward Dugger, Jr., June, 1940; MS036.001.087.00001.04430; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 87)
      Print is in Munro Collection, box 087, p. 130, #13816
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 70, 1940-06 -- 1940-10; MS036.001.088.00001 (Volume 88)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 71, 1940-10 -- 1941-03; MS036.001.089.00001 (Volume 89)
    box 1 of 2
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 71, 1940-10 -- 1941-03; MS036.001.090.00001 (Volume 90)
    box 2 of 2
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 73, 1941-05 -- 1941-06; MS036.001.092.00001 (Volume 92)
    Probably volume 73, but marked as 72.; Alumni day news clippings p31
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 74, 1941 -- 1942; MS036.001.093.00001; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 93)
    - Jackson students practice first aid, 1941; MS036.001.093.00001.00834; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 93)
      In Munro Scrapbook v. 74, p. 16; Jackson Students apply practical first aid after completing a 10 weeks course given by the Red Cross
      World War, 1939-1945; photographic print; Jackson College
    - Collecting for the Red Cross, 1941; MS036.001.093.00001.00835; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 93)
      Mounted in Munro Scrapbook v. 74, p. 16. Tufts Student Council members solicit for the Red Cross drive
      World War, 1939-1945; photographic print; Student Council
    - Sailors walking up Memorial Steps, 1941; MS036.001.093.00001.00836; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 93)
      Mounted in Munro Scrapbook, v. 74 p. 130.
      World War, 1939-1945; photographic print
    - NROTC parade down College Avenue, 1941; MS036.001.093.00001.00837; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 93)
      Date is approximate; 8x10 mounted in Munro scrapbook v. 74, p. 125
      World War, 1939-1945; photographic print; NROTC
    - Students practice air raid, 1942; MS036.001.093.00001.00838; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 93)
      Mounted in Munro Scrapbook v. 74, p.
      World War, 1939-1945; Students; People; photographic print
    - Captain Preston B. Haines, 1942; MS036.001.093.00001.00934; Unknown (Volume 93)
      8 x 10 mounted on 10 x 12 paper in M.S. Munro, Photographic History of Tufts College Volume 74 pg. 37
      -NROTC; World War, 1939-1945; photographic print; Haines, Captain Preston B.; Navy V-12 Program; Reserve Officers Training Corps (Navy)
    - Captain C. H. J. Keppler, 1942; MS036.001.093.00001.00935; Unknown (Volume 93)
      8 x 10 mounted on 10 x 12 paper in M.S. Munro, Photographic History of Tufts College Volume 74 pg. 36
      World War, 1939-1945; NROTC; photographic print; Keppler, Captain C. H. J.; Navy V-12 Program; Reserve Officers Training Corps (Navy)
    - NROTC with Flags, 1941 -- 1942; MS036.001.093.00001.00936; Unknown (Volume 93)
      8 x 10 mounted on 10 x 12 paper in M.S. Munro, Photographic History of Tufts College Volume 74 pg. 119
      World War, 1939-1945; NROTC; photographic print; Navy V-12 Program; Reserve Officers Training Corps (Navy)
    - Captain Preston B. Haines and Captain Richard D. Kirkpatrick, USMC, E1940 and USN ROTC Flag, 1942; MS036.001.093.00001.00951; Unknown (Volume 93)
      5 x 7 mounted on 10 x 12 paper in M.S. Munro, Photographic History of Tufts College Volume 74 pg. 100
      World War, 1939-1945; NROTC; photographic print; Haines, Captain Preston B.; Kirkpatrick, Captain Richard D.; Navy V-12 Program; Reserve Officers Training Corps (Navy)
    - NROTC Training on Mystic Lakes, 1942; MS036.001.093.00001.00952; Unknown (Volume 93, Box Shared 42)
      8 x 10 mounted on 10 x 12 paper in M.S. Munro, Photographic History of Tufts College Volume 74 pg. 114
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 75, 1943 -- 1944; MS036.001.094.00001 (Volume 94)
    - Civilian students: Victor G. Laties, Robert L. Nichols, Philip A. Bugler, Edward F. M. Wong, Charles L. Beckles, and Charles W. More, 1940; MS036.001.094.00001.04419; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 94)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 94, p. 56
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Laties, Victor G.; Nichols, Robert L.; Bugler, Philip A.; Wong, Edward F. M.; Beckles, Charles L.; Moore, Charles W.
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, general landscape views, vol. 01, 1928; MS036.001.095.00001 (Volume 95)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, landscape views, vol. 02, 1928; MS036.001.096.00001 (Volume 96)
    - Two student surveyors, 1928; MS036.001.096.00001.00100; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 96)
      Munro Scrapbook vol. 2 Landscape Views, p. 73 photograph # 2645
      People; Students; copy negative
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, miscellaneous views, vol. 03, 1927; MS036.001.097.00001 (Volume 97)
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, vol. 48, 1936-05 -- 1936-06; MS036.001.098.00001 (Volume 98)
    Alumni day, pp 48-49, 57-67
    - Robert W. Hill, 1904; MS036.001.098.00001.00399; Unknown (Volume 98)
      in Munro Photograph Scrapbook v.48 1946, p. 51
      People; photographic print
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 23, 1929-03 -- 1929-06; MS036.001.099.00001 (Volume 99)
    Alpha Tau Omega, 143.
    - Margaret Reynolds, Jackson baseball catcher, May 18, 1929; MS036.001.099.00001.01555; Munro, Melville S. (Box MS036 Shared 1)
      From MS036/001-099 p. 91
      Athletics; Baseball (Women's); photographic print; Reynolds, Margaret; Jackson College
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 24, 1929-06 -- 1929-11; MS036.001.100.00001 (Volume 100)
    Alumni procession photos, pp 18-19
    - Students in procession, Ballou Hall, 1929-06-17; MS036.001.100.00001.04360; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 100)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 100, p. 35, #8254
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 25, 1929-11 -- 1929-12; MS036.001.101.00001 (Volume 101)
    [Alumnae Hall] Artist's sketch
    - John T. Macrery, Stanley St. Clair Mullins, Alfred J. Judge, Albert W. Roach, and Elwood Horne, freshmen liberal arts students, class of 1933, 1929; MS036.001.101.00001.04361; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 101)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 101, p. 5, #8257
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Macrery, John T.; Mullins, Stanley St. Clair; Judge, Alfred J.; Roach, Albert W.; Horne, Elwood
    - Robert Lewis, Joseph Walker, J. George Fanelli, Ralph L. Dockendorff, and Peter Kalustian, freshman engineers, 1929; MS036.001.101.00001.04362; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 101)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 101, p. 12, #8285
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Lewis, Robert; Walker, Joseph; Fanelli, J. George; Dockendorff, Ralph; Kalustian, Peter
    - Freshmen engineers at Memorial Steps and Hodgdon Gate, 1929-11-19; MS036.001.101.00001.04363; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 101)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 101, p. 65, #8563
    - Liberal Arts freshmen, Goddard Chapel, 1929-11-24; MS036.001.101.00001.04364; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 101)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 101, p. 69, #8567
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 26, 1930-01 -- 1930-04; MS036.001.102.00001 (Volume 102)
    House party photos Alpha Tau Omega, 116. Alpha Tau Omega, 1.
    - Construction of glider, 1930-04-23; MS036.001.102.00001.03177; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 102)
      Munro Box 045, vol. 26, p. 146. In photo from left to right are Gillon, Gray and Mitchell.
      People; photographic print; Munro, Melville S.; Dept. of Mechanical Engineering; College of Engineering
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 27, 1930-05 -- 1930-06-16; MS036.001.103.00001 (Volume 103)
    Alumni day, pp89-95
    - John J. Costruio, William C. Button, Lajarus, M. Phillips, and Charles W. Thomas, and Horace Hollister, September, 1930; MS036.001.103.00001.04340; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 103)
      Date is approximate; Print is in Munro Collection, Box 103 p. 127, #9031
      Students; photographic print; Black students; Costruio, John J.; Button, WIlliam C.; Phillips, Lajarus M.; Thomas, Charles W.; Hollister, Horace
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 28, 1930-09 -- 1930-12; MS036.001.104.00001 (Volume 104)
    - Tufts sophomore engineers in front of Memorial Steps at Hodgdon Gate, 1930-10-22; MS036.001.104.00001.04339; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 104)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 104 p. 46, #9138
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 29, 1930-12 -- 1931-04; MS036.001.105.00001 (Volume 105)
    Alpha Tau Omega, 6.
    - Alfred C. Lane with rock in a laboratory, 1931-02-27; MS036.001.105.00001.02724; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 105)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 29, Box No. 48, Pg. 77
      People; Faculty; photographic print; Lane, Alfred Church; Dept. of Geology
    - A thesis project for the Department of Mechanical Engineering, 1930-04-23; MS036.001.105.00001.03332; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 105)
      Munro Scrapbook: Vol. 29, Box No. 45, Pg. 147; left to right: Henry F. Gray, John W. Gillon, and Donald H. Mitchell
      People; Faculty; Students; photographic print; Gray, Henry F.; Gillon, John W.; Mitchell, Donald H.; Dept. of Mechanical Engineering
  - Photographic history of Tufts College, Vol. 30, 1931-05 -- 1931-06; MS036.001.106.00001 (Volume 106)
    Alumni day photos, pp 95-101
    - Tufts varsity tennis team, 1931-06-04; MS036.001.106.00001.04367; Munro, Melville S. (Volume 106)
      Print is in Munro Collection, Box 106, p. 65, #9466
- Afield with a camera, 1908 -- 1940; 1930 -- 1937; MS036.002; 3.5 Linear Feet; 6 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains albums with photographs, newspaper clippings, campus event advertisements, and publications from daily life on campus primarily between 1930 and 1937. Each album is titled "Afield With a Camera" and is organized around a particular subject or theme. Also includes Stone & Webster Journal and several Thomas Edison newsletters.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - Benson's animal team, 1935 -- 1940; MS036.002.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Eugene B. Bowen: a loyal Tufts alumnus, 1924; MS036.002.025.00002 (Box 25)
    - The Bowen Gate Decorated for the Dedication Ceremony, 1924; MS036.002.025.00002.00367; Munro, Melville S. (Box Shared 86)
      from Munro, Afield with a Camera-Bowen A Loyal Tufts Man,17
      Gates; image/tiff
  - The Chelsea conflagration [fire], 1908; MS036.002.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Through the years with baseball coach "Ken" Nash, 1920 -- 1940; MS036.002.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - The desert of Maine, 1937; MS036.002.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Edward Dugger athlete, 1938-05-04 -- 1940-06-01; MS036.002.026.00001 (Box 26)
    - Tufts freshman Edward "Eddie" Dugger, at Tufts College, 1938-05-04; MS036.002.026.00001.01413; Munro, Melville S. (Box 26)
      Edward Dugger; Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/002-026#001-pg. 5
      Students; photographic print; Dugger, Edward
    - Edward Dugger wins the 220-yard low hurdles at Harvard Stadium, 1940-06-01; MS036.002.026.00001.01435; Munro, Melville S. (Box 26)
      Edward Dugger;Melville S. Munro Collection - MS036/002-026#001-pg. 22
      Athletics; Track (Men's); photographic print; Dugger, Edward; Harvard University
  - The first water power grant in New Hampshire: for a dam in the town of Hampton Falls, 1930; MS036.002.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - The book of hobbies, 1940; MS036.002.026.00003 (Box 26)